

Behnam Khoshsafar

SENIOR JAVA DEVELOPER

PROFILE

Nationality: Iranian
Birth Date: 09/06/1990

A passionate and hard-working developer with experience in designing and developing software in Java since 2014.

Participated in implementing different types of applications specializing in the banking industry. Skilled in Java, Spring Boot, Hibernate, REST, Message Queue, RabbitMQ, GIT, Relational database, NoSql, and Linux.

EDUCATION

Master of Science from Qom University in Information technology - E-commerce from September 2012 to February 2015.

Bachelor of Science from Kurdestan University in Information technology from September 2008 to September 2012.

LANGUAGES

English

Persian

CONTACT

Email: b.khoshsafar@gmail.com

Mobile: +98 991 413 1042

LinkedIn: Khoshsafar's profile

WORK EXPERIENCE

Snapp!

Senior Java Developer

Sep 2020 - Present

- We are working on developing payment hub for Snapp products to facilitate user daily payments.

MyDigipay

Senior Java Developer

Mar 2019 - Aug 2020

- I worked as a member of the Credit team.
- I designed and implemented the Installment module.
- I designed and implemented the KYC(Know your customer) module.

Sava Arman Kish (Bitex)

Senior Java Developer

July 2018 - Mar 2019

- I designed and implemented the Order module.
- I designed and implemented the Notification module.
- I designed and implemented the Report module.

Navaco (Maskan Bank)

Java Developer

Feb 2017 - July 2018

- I worked as a member of the Lending team.
- I designed and implemented lending overnight calculation.
- I designed and implemented the Letter of Credit subsystem.

Hamgam Corporate Group

Java Developer

April 2014 - Jan 2017

- I designed and implemented the Sale module.
- I designed and implemented the Inventory module.



Behnam Khoshsafar SENIOR JAVA DEVELOPER

PROGRAMMING SKILLS

Java	Spring
Design Patterns	Spring Boot
Microservices	Spring MVC
Test Driven Development	Spring Batch
JUnit / Mockito	Spring Security
WireMock	Spring Cloud Config
Gatling	Spring Cloud Netflix
Docker and Docker Compose	Spring Cloud Gateway
CI / CD	Spring Cloud Sleuth
Git	Spring Cloud Zipkin
Jenkins	Spring WebFlux
Gitlab	Reactive Programming
OpenShift	Concurrent Programming
Maven	Spring Data
RabbitMQ	MySQL
Elastic Stack (ELK)	Oracle
RESTful Web Services	MongoDB
Swagger	Redis
UML / Agile and RUP Methodologies	Hibernate
Lending System Developer	Liquibase
CORE Banking Systems	Eureka / Ribbon / Hystrix / Zuul Netflix